<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Daisuke Aramaki's Blog</title>
 <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog"/>
 <updated>2018-10-28T21:52:43+09:00</updated>
 <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog</id>
 <author>
   <name>Daisuke Aramaki</name>
   <email>murugan.prem.k@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Work related things</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/28/daisuke-aramaki-cv-online"/>
   <updated>2018-10-28T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/28/daisuke-aramaki-cv-online</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So, I think the CV page is finally coming along nicely. It should give you folks an idea about my qualifications and the kind of work I do. As I had mentioned on the CV page, I do not have clearance to state or talk openly about some of my work. Interested folks can drop me an email and I will send my unedited CV. Given the remote nature of my work schedule right now, doing extra projects should be no hassle whatsoever. So, if you are looking for someone with my kind of expertise to look into something, please feel free. Quantitative consulting, feasibility analysis, reliability study, fundamental research - you name it. Due to the highly abstract and theoretical aspect of my education background it was  easier to adapt to working in different domains, thereby diversifying my portfolio. Because fundamentally, most systems reveal a familiar mathematical structure and the only difference is the stuff you add or remove to model them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m completely self-taught in programming and never learned things like, data structures, algorithm design or kernel internals at the university, yet deal with such topics regularly and quite successfully as well. So, I don’t write beautiful code and I really don’t think I have to. IT guys should do that. Functionality and efficiency are more important for me and I always strive my best to make my code conform to these attributes. I will talk more about these things in a new blog post tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy reading my posts and do drop me a line if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Testing Github Pages</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/22/daisuke-aramaki-testing-site"/>
   <updated>2018-10-22T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/22/daisuke-aramaki-testing-site</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have started playing around a bit with this setup and hopefully I’ll be able to tune the site to meet my expectations in a week or so. Please keep watching. While you are here, please check out my other blog - &lt;a href=&quot;https://theoretischephysiker.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;A Physicist’s Wastebasket&lt;/a&gt;. I talk about my further interests, physics and some mundane day to day happenings there. I will use this place for my professional contributions and talk exclusively about technology related matters. Nothing more nothing less!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Mad Dog Daisuke Aramaki launches site</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/21/daisuke-aramaki-site-launched"/>
   <updated>2018-10-21T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/21/daisuke-aramaki-site-launched</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Well. Finally got around to putting this old website together. Neat thing about it - powered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and I can use Markdown to author my posts. It actually is a lot easier than I thought it was going to be.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
