<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Daisuke Aramaki's Blog</title>
 <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog"/>
 <updated>2018-11-06T00:50:19+09:00</updated>
 <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog</id>
 <author>
   <name>Daisuke Aramaki</name>
   <email>murugan.prem.k@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Career Diversity - Boon or Bane?</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/29/daisuke-aramaki-career-diversity-boon-or-bane"/>
   <updated>2018-10-29T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/29/daisuke-aramaki-career-diversity-boon or bane?</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/article-emba-career-paths-are-becoming-more-diverse-615x370.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Diverse&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive align-center&quot; height=&quot;180px&quot; width=&quot;300x&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can relate to this personally. You see, I have worked in many roles across various domains in my career. Although, I was addressing similar questions in tackling problems in different industries. Furthermore, as I had mentioned in my previous blog post, most problems were mathematically analogous. So, it was not that difficult to adapt and after a while I started to see a strong concurrence in such problems. This convergence was more pronounced during the time I was a management consultant. My boss thought that I could address multi-industry issues simultaneously due to my diverse domain experience. While stressful, it actually worked out fine. Every client I worked with during that time was very happy with my contribution and a few of us even became great friends. Our bosses really liked what a couple of us were doing and decided to create an independent cross-functional, cross-industry model development and analysis subsidiary to kick the whole thing up a notch. This will always remain as one of my biggest career accomplishments. Then, as you are preparing yourself to take your career to the next level, your world comes crashing down due to a personal tragedy. I had to come back to India immediately. Although difficult to understand it then, I am absolutely at peace now with how things changed so suddenly. Also, I am very happy and proud the way the organization we influenced creating, has grown leaps and bounds in the last couple of years. They are doing some exceptional work across multiple industrial domains and have won a few prestigious consulting awards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All those happenings made me believe that career diversity is actually a good thing. Especially now, where boundaries between certain jobs are dissolving, it does seem like such a diversity would be an asset. However, based on what I see here, it looks like it will take a bit longer to reach that level of flexibility with our Indian firms. Although I am quite happy with where I am right now, my wife hates it. Since I work remotely, I have to keep odd hours and it is certainly cutting into our family life. My current boss is very understanding and she is OK with me looking for something local and even told me to take some fully paid time off to focus on the job search. Last week, I identified a few positions and have applied. No response from any of them yet. I went directly to a small consulting firm to give my portfolio and even met the director of the firm and spoke with him for a couple of hours. He told me he could recruit me only next February. So that’s that. Back in EU, most companies facilitate speculatively applying for a job if they do not have any openings currently for your skillset. Here, such a concept is almost non existent. You have to either start hunting on the web for a HR’s email address to send the application directly, or call the control channel requesting them to patch you through to someone from HR!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Work related things</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/28/daisuke-aramaki-cv-online"/>
   <updated>2018-10-28T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/28/daisuke-aramaki-cv-online</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So, I think the CV page is finally coming along nicely. It should give you folks an idea about my qualifications and the kind of work I do. As I had mentioned on the CV page, I do not have clearance to state or talk openly about some of my work. Interested folks can drop me an email and I will send my unedited CV. Given the remote nature of my work schedule right now, doing extra projects should be no hassle whatsoever. So, if you are looking for someone with my kind of expertise to look into something, please feel free. Quantitative consulting, feasibility analysis, reliability study, fundamental research - you name it. Due to the highly abstract and theoretical aspect of my education background it was  easier to adapt to working in different domains, thereby diversifying my portfolio. Because fundamentally, most systems reveal a familiar mathematical structure and the only difference is the stuff you add or remove to model them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m completely self-taught in programming and never learned things like, data structures, algorithm design or kernel internals at the university, yet deal with such topics regularly and quite successfully as well. So, I don’t write beautiful code and I really don’t think I have to. IT guys should do that. Functionality and efficiency are more important for me and I always strive my best to make my code conform to these attributes. I will talk more about these things in a new blog post tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy reading my posts and do drop me a line if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Testing Github Pages</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/22/daisuke-aramaki-testing-site"/>
   <updated>2018-10-22T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/22/daisuke-aramaki-testing-site</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have started playing around a bit with this setup and hopefully I’ll be able to tune the site to meet my expectations in a week or so. Please keep watching. While you are here, please check out my other blog - &lt;a href=&quot;https://oldmanaramaki.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;A Physicist’s Wastebasket&lt;/a&gt;. I talk about my further interests, physics and some mundane day to day happenings there. I will use this place for my professional contributions and talk exclusively about technology related matters. Nothing more nothing less!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Mad Dog Daisuke Aramaki launches site</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/21/daisuke-aramaki-site-launched"/>
   <updated>2018-10-21T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/21/daisuke-aramaki-site-launched</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Well. Finally got aroung to putting this old website together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://static.comicvine.com/uploads/scale_small/1/10135/264528-195150-aramaki.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Daisuke Aramaki&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; height=&quot;139px&quot; width=&quot;120px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neat thing about it - powered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and I can use Markdown to author my posts. It actually is a lot easier than I thought it was going to be.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
