<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Daisuke Aramaki's Blog</title>
 <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog"/>
 <updated>2018-10-28T06:52:00+09:00</updated>
 <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog</id>
 <author>
   <name>Daisuke Aramaki</name>
   <email>murugan.prem.k@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Work related things</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/28/daisuke-aramaki-cv-online"/>
   <updated>2018-10-28T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/28/daisuke-aramaki-cv-online</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So, I think the CV page is finally set up the way I wanted. It should give you folks an idea about my qualifications and the kind of work I do. As I had mentioned on the CV page, I do not have clearance to state or talk openly about some of my work. Interested folks can drop me an email and I will send my unedited CV. Given the remote nature of my work schedule right now, doing extra projects should be no hassle whatsoever. So, if you are looking for someone with my kind of expertise to look into something, please feel free. Quant research, feasibility review, reliability study, fundamental analysis - you name it. I can contribute. Due to the highly abstract and theoretical aspect of my education background it is easier to diversify my portfolio by working in different areas. Because, mathematically, physically all are one and the same, you just change the stuff you add or remove. Sometimes, it’s just different semantics. You get the drift?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would also like to mention that I am not a programmer! I code a lot, yes. But the code is just a tool to check if my quant strategy or mathematical methodology captures the reality of the problem in hand. I really don’t give a rat’s furry behind if one of my try-catch blocks hurts your eyes or my Perl indentation drives you nuts. I’m completely self-taught in programming and never learned data structures or kernel programming at the university, yet deal with such topics quite regularly and deal with them successfully. So, if you want beautiful code, I’m so not your guy. But if you are looking for someone who writes efficient programs that do exactly what they are supposed to do, reflecting on the complete understanding of the problem in hand, I’m absolutely your guy and I would love to work with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way, tabs over spaces man!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Testing Github Pages</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/22/daisuke-aramaki-testing-site"/>
   <updated>2018-10-22T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/22/daisuke-aramaki-testing-site</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have started playing around a bit with this setup and hopefully I’ll be able to tune the site to meet my expectations in a week or so. Please keep watching. While you are here, please check out my other blog - &lt;a href=&quot;https://theoretischephysiker.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;A Physicist’s Wastebasket&lt;/a&gt;. I talk about my further interests, physics and some mundane day to day happenings there. I will use this place for my professional contributions and talk exclusively about technology related matters. Nothing more nothing less!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Mad Dog Daisuke Aramaki launches site</title>
   <link href="http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io/blog/2018/10/21/daisuke-aramaki-site-launched"/>
   <updated>2018-10-21T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
   <id>http://DaisukeAramaki.github.io//blog/2018/10/21/daisuke-aramaki-site-launched</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Well. Finally got around to putting this old website together. Neat thing about it - powered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and I can use Markdown to author my posts. It actually is a lot easier than I thought it was going to be.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
